{
  "Contacts": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a violent or dangerous kick?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The kick does not need to hit a player to be dangerous.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegaly hurdling or attempting to hurdle ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A hurdle is defined as jumping or diving fully over any person, and is not legal on a player that is standing up.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a reckless contact ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "QuestionViolentContactExplanation",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is a penalty for an illegal contact on a helpless receiver ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "An helpless receiver is defined as a receiver who is in the process of catching a ball that is in the air.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is a penalty a charge or tackle on a helpless receiver ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A helpless receiver is defined as a receiver who is in the process of catching a ball that is in the air.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a standard contact violation ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "This penalty may be reduced\r\nThis penalty may be augmented\r\nYellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The penalty shall be reduced to a back to hoops if the fouling player immediatly correct his position, and augmented to a red card if the play was egregious.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a minor illegal interposition ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "8",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal interposition ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "9",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegally interacting with a knocked out player ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "10",
      "QuestionText": "Which penalty should the attacking player receive ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nDefending player should receive the same penalty\r\nTurnover",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player is allowed to charge another player by having their foot leave the ground if the attempt was to score a goal.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/wearypowerfulhammerkop?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "12",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should green player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Body blocking that way is legal even without a ball involved. Carefull, a body block has force applied AFTER contact is initiated, not before.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/fastwickedcoelacanth?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "13",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should green player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Push a player that way is legal even without a ball involed. Carefull, a push should not involve excessive force or force before the contact.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/shimmeringthankfullhasaapso?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "14",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Yellow player already has force as the contact begin, qualifying this contact for a charge. Charges are illegal without a ball involved.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/plusheasygoingbooby?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "15",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Green player had her hand on the ball, thus making the kick illegal.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/reflectingimmaculatecaiman?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "16",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Green player had to remove her hand to not get kicked, making it an illegal kick.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/adolescentanybunny?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "17",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "While green player's hand was close, yellow player hit the ball before it was touching the ball.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/largeembellishedgalapagossealion?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "18",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "While yellow player kicks the ball as green player touched it, the kick was severely restrained when yellow player realized it would be an illegal kick. In this case, use no harm no foul.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/simplisticspiritedcero?autoplay=1"
    }
  ],
  "Definition": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true for a blue card call ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Any ball acted upon or prevented to get by the fouling player is turned over\r\nPlayer is released after a minute\r\nPlayer is released after getting scored",
      "BadAnswers": "A second blue card is upgraded to a yellow card\r\nQuaffle is turned over",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true for a yellow card call ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "A second yellow card provokes an ejection.\r\nAny ball acted upon or prevented to get by the fouling player is turned over\r\nQuaffle is turned over\r\nPlayer is released after a minute\r\nPlayer is released after getting scored",
      "BadAnswers": "",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true for a red card call ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Any ball acted upon or prevented to get by the fouling player is turned over\r\nQuaffle is turned over\r\nA Player is released after two minutes",
      "BadAnswers": "A Player is released after a minute\r\nA Player is released after getting scored",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Since the red carded player may not play the match again, it is a different player that must go into the penalty box and be released.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "BallInteraction": [
    {
      "Publci ID": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegaly acting on a dead quaffle ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal bludger bat or block ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal bludger swat ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an unintentionnal natural motion violation ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an intentionnal natural motion violation ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal use of a ball of one's position ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "7",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a minor failure to avoid a propelled quaffle ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "8",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a failure to avoid a propelled quaffle ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "9",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an incidental interposition ball interference ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "10",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an interposition ball interference ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Publci ID": "11",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a second kick ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No Penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "DelayOfGame": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a delay of game ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "Keeper": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What are the keeper-specific privilegies ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "That player is immune to KO by bludgers\r\nThat player cannot be contacted, interacted with, or stolen the quaffle while he is the sole possessor of it",
      "BadAnswers": "That player can kick the ball any number of time\r\nThat player can block a bludger\r\nThat player gets the quaffle back if it goes out of bound after a save",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A keeper only has those privilegies when they're in their keeper zone, and their team either is not on offense or no player from that team possessed the quaffle outside their keeper zone. ",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "Can the keeper start the attack?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yes",
      "BadAnswers": "No",
      "AnswerExplanation": "After the ball was passed as the keeper requested, the keeper controls the quaffle inside his keeper zone, game can proceed.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/similargeneralacornwoodpecker?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "Can the keeper start the attack?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No",
      "BadAnswers": "Yes",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Since the ball was touched by another player or official after the goal, the keeper needs to get back into his keeper zone before proceeding with the game.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/tandearestimperialeagle?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "Can the keeper start the attack?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yes",
      "BadAnswers": "No",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Since no one touched the quaffle after the goal, the keeper can start the attack from her own half of the field.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/variablesharpleonberger?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "Can the keeper start the attack?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yes",
      "BadAnswers": "No",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The keeper correctly goes back into her own half of the field. At this point, she's the first one that touched the ball after the goal and is in her own half, so she can start the attack.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/lividbetterkodiakbear?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nTurnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "It is illegal to steal a ball from a protected keeper.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/unimportantshamelessandeancondor?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Keeper is not beat",
      "BadAnswers": "KeeperBeatFeetInAnswer2\r\nKeeperBeatFeetInAnswer1\r\nKeeperBeatFeetInAnswer4",
      "AnswerExplanation": "While the keeper is mostly out of his zone when hit, his feet is still in, so she is still protected.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/infantilethreadbarebeardeddragon?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "8",
      "QuestionText": "What penalty should yellow player receive?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nTurnover",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The keeper stopped being protected once out of the zone, and cannot become protected again until the opposing team controls the quaffle.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/deadlycompleteboubou?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "9",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Play should keep going",
      "BadAnswers": "The keeper should get the quaffle, ending yellow's attack",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The keeper must be the sole owner of the quaffle to be protected. Since yellow player is contesting it, play keeps going.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/hardliquidindianpalmsquirrel?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "10",
      "QuestionText": "Can the keeper start the attack?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No",
      "BadAnswers": "Yes",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The keeper cannot restart from the opposing half of the field.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/elatedunsungdoe?autoplay=1"
    }
  ],
  "KO": [
    {
      "Public ID": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for willfully ignoring being knocked out ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegally contacting an opponent with a held bludger?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for violating the knockout procedure ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Repeat procedure",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Violating it multiple times or willingly increases the penalty.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for intentionally or repeatedly violating the knockout procedure ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Repeat procedure\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegally interacting with play while knocked out ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for making an illegal contact while knocked out ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "7",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a struck beater violation?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "Other": [
    {
      "Public ID": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for encroaching the pitch ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the lower and upper limit of the number of player in a team ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "7\r\n21",
      "BadAnswers": "6\r\n22",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What happens when a team falls below the necessary number of player during a game ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The team must forfeit",
      "BadAnswers": "The team must play with fewer than the necessary amount of player\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "This is also true if the team has more than 7 players, but cannot respect the 4-maximum rule.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a team that has an illegal set of player in play ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow card for the speaking captain",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover and correct the team composition\r\nBlue card for the speaking captain\r\nNo penalty",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for intentionnaly failing to send a seeker into the game ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow card for the speaking captain",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover and immediatly send a seeker\r\nBlue card for the speaking captain\r\nRed card for the speaking captain\r\nNo penalty",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What of the following is true when correcting an illegal set of player ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The team must change as few players as possible",
      "BadAnswers": "The team may change any number of player, as ling as this result in a legal set of players\r\nThe team cannot change players immediatly, but must sub players as soon as the game restart",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "7",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal substitution ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Repeat procedure\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "An illegal susbtitution must affect play, otherwise it is a substitution violation.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "8",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for feigning an injury ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "9",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an unintentionnal sideline interference ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "10",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for ignoring a ref directive ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "This is also true for assist refs, snitch ref and snitch runner.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "11",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an unsportsmanlike conduct ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "12",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an egregious unsportsmanlike conduct ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public ID": "13",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the repeated use of explicit or vulgar language ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "If it's French, it's probably a swear word.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "FieldsAndEquipment": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for knowingly playing with a broken broom ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for entering play with illegally long or sharp fingernails ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Too long fingernails can be seen when the hand is palm up",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for entering play without wearing mandatory equipment ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for removing a mandatory equipment while in play ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for failing to replace a lost headband ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The player may finish the play before adjusting the headband",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for playing with an illegal equipment ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for using an equipment that was specified as illegal by the tournament organisator ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "ImmunityAndGuarding": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a third bludger interference ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Double bludger turnover\r\nQuaffle Turnover\r\nBack to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "One of the turned over bludger should usually be the one that was on the ground.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an improper immunity claim ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a minor illegal immunity claim ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "QuestionMinorIllegalImmunityClaimExplanation",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal immunity claim ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "QuestionIllegalImmunityClaimExplanation",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an immunity violation ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "An immunity violation is defined as a player that legally claimed immunity, then did not correctly retrieved the third bludger.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue beater is still immune and may retrieve the bludger",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue beater is not immune anymore but not KO\r\nThe beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Nothing in the rules prevent a player from trying to beat another immune player, as long as this does not transgress another rule.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/remotefoolishhartebeest?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue beater committed an improper immunity claim and must be sent back to hoops.",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue beater claim is valid and he can keep playing.\r\nThe beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The bludger still being live, claiming immunity is illegal. Bludger becomes dead only when it touches the ground.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/unkemptfantasticatlanticblackgoby?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "8",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue beater committed an improper immunity claim and must be sent back to hoops.",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue beater claim is valid and he can keep playing.\r\nThe beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The bludger still being live, claiming immunity is illegal. Bludger becomes dead only when it touches the ground.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/knobbyresponsibleblesbok?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "9",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Beater that claimed immunity is immune",
      "BadAnswers": "Beater that claimed immunity is beat\r\nThe beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A claim made before the opposing beater made the bludger live is valid, even if that player already started the movement.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/crazysoftechidna?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "10",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Beater that claimed immunity is beat",
      "BadAnswers": "Beater that claimed immunity is immune\r\nThe beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A claim made when a bludger is live does not make the player immune to that bludger.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/ambitiousmintyamericanbobtail?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "11",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue player's claim of immunity is invalid, he should be send back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue player's claim of immunity is valid\r\nBlue player's claim of immunity is invalid, he should be given a blue card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Blue player cannot claim immunity while 2 bludgers are dead. However, since the claim did not affect the game yet, the penalty is reduced to a minor invalid immunity claim.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/decimalposhbedlingtonterrier?autoplay=1",
      "Include": "n"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "12",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Claim is valid, no penalty.",
      "BadAnswers": "One blue player should be penalized\r\nBoth blue players should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "When both beaters in a team claim immunity, one must lower his fist immediatly to avoid a penalty.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/eminentflakyflickertailsquirrel?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "13",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "One blue beater should be penalized",
      "BadAnswers": "Claim is valid, no penalty. \r\nBoth blue beaters should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "If no beater immediatly lowers his fist, one beater commits a minor invalid immunity claim and should be send back to hoops.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/pastharmfulbufflehead?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "14",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue beater that got the ball should be penalized\r\nBlue beater that raised is fist should be penalized\r\nBoth blue beaters should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Nothing prevents the beater that did not claimed immunity to get the third bludger.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/minormarvelousfawn?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "15",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The beater that claimed immunity should be penalized",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "It is forbidden to take any other action than retrieving the bludger when claiming immunity.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/halfcandiddeer?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "16",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The kick was valid, no penalty.",
      "BadAnswers": "The kick was valid and blue is KO, but yellow player should be penalized\r\nThe kick was not valid, yellow player should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Shooting the bludger is a valid way of retrieving it, so no penalty should be issued here.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/variablecourageouscassowary?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "17",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The kick is valid, no penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "The kick is invalid, yellow player should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Kicking to the player's hoops is a valid way of retrieving the bludger",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/denseunlawfulaustraliancattledog?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "18",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.\r\nThe beater is still immune",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty for blue player",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Taking the third bludger without having used its own bludger in a valid way is a 3rd bludger interference",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/wealthygrimyiberianmidwifetoad?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "19",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The beater gathering the bludgers commits no foul",
      "BadAnswers": "The beater gathering the bludgers commits a foul by getting the 3rd bludger\r\nThe beater gathering the bludgers commits a foul by getting the 2sd bludger",
      "AnswerExplanation": "As there was always 2 dead bludgers at the same time, there can be no 3rd bludger interference.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/selfishwearyinexpectatumpleco?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "20",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Taking the third bludger without having used its own bludger in a valid way is a 3rd bludger interference",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/cornythoroughchimpanzee?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "21",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "The beater who threw the bludger commited a third bludger interference.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/forkedastonishingankole?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "22",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The beater that claimed immunity should be penalized",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "It is forbidden to take any other action than retrieving the bludger when claiming immunity.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/yawningrichaddax?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "23",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Green player is beat.\r\nYellow player should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Even when the player lowers its fist, they stay immune until they retrieve the bludger.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/windinglinedarmadillo?autoplay=1"
    }
  ],
  "OutOfBoundaries": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for propelling a ball with the intent of sending any ball out of bounds ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for intentionally or blatantly ignoring a “boundary” call ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for intentionally or egregiously illegally going or remaining out of bounds ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an inbounding procedure violation ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBack to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegally physically preventing the inbounding player from re-entering the pitch ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Back to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "Which way is correct to inbound a bludger?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Clip1",
      "BadAnswers": "Clip2",
      "AnswerExplanation": "InboundingBludgerExplanation",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/oldfavorableisabellinewheatear?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBack to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Caution: if the opposing team controls two bludgers, this bludger cannot be turned over. Only apply the back to hoops penalty in this case.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/coldfarawaygoral?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "8",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow player should retrieve the bludger",
      "BadAnswers": "Green player should retrieve the bludger",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Yellow player is closest when the bludger goes out, so she gets priority.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/necessaryposhfinnishspitz?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "9",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Green player should retrieve the bludger",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow player should retrieve the bludger",
      "AnswerExplanation": "While yellow player is closest when the bludger goes out, she is not elligible because she already owns a bludger. The next closest player is green, so she can retrieve the bludger thrown.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/hatefulglisteningjapanesebeetle?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "10",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow player should retrieve the bludger",
      "BadAnswers": "Green player should retrieve the bludger",
      "AnswerExplanation": "As green is the closest elligible player when the bludger goes out, she is the one who can retrieve the bludger at the start. However, after the beat, the next closest elligible player become the yellow player.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/embarrassedfrighteningeasternglasslizard?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "11",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow player should be penalized",
      "BadAnswers": "Green player is beat\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Once outside the pitch, green player becomes immune. Yellow player is willingly throwing a ball with the intention of sending it out of pitch, which is illegal. (Blue card)",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/wickedglamorousdiamondbackrattlesnake?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "12",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Green player is beat\r\nYellow player should be penalized",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A feet outside is enough for green player to become immune. Consequently, Yellow player is willingly throwing a ball with the intention of sending it out of pitch, which is illegal. (Blue card)",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/ampleneatbass?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "13",
      "QuestionText": "Which way is correct to inbound a quaffle?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Clip 2",
      "BadAnswers": "Clip 1",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A quaffle has to be inbounded to the point where it left the field.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/generalillustriousivorybackedwoodswallow?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "14",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBack to hoops",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The quaffle cannot be thrown in. Also, the player has 5 seconds to inbound any ball.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/shamelesscomfortablegnatcatcher?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "15",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The green player should retrieve the quaffle",
      "BadAnswers": "The yellow player should retrieve the quaffle",
      "AnswerExplanation": "For the quaffle, except some specific cases, the team that can retrieve the quaffle is always the team that did not threw it outside.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/secondhandtestycarpenterant?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "16",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Green player is beat",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow player should be penalized\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The green player does not become immune until she reaches outside the field.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/disgustinglimitedclownanemonefish?autoplay=1"
    }
  ],
  "Process": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for changing position or location after brooms down, at the beginning of a match ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for moving or taking hold of a ball during a brooms down ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Players that already held a ball may keep holding it.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal timeout request ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nRed Card\r\nYellow Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What happens when a turnover is called, but no elligible player may receive the turned-over ball ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The ball is placed at the hoops of the fouled team",
      "BadAnswers": "The ball is unplayable until the fouled team plays it\r\nThe turnover is cancelled",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "Two players of the same team are in the penalty box serving a yellow penalty when their team get scored against?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The player with the least remaining time is released",
      "BadAnswers": "Both players are released\r\nThe team chooses who gets released first",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "A player do a blue or yellow card offense causing an advantage. After the fouled team scores, the referee gives the card to the player.",
      "GoodAnswers": "The player keeps playing",
      "BadAnswers": "The player goes to the penalty box\r\nThe player must go back to hoops",
      "AnswerExplanation": "Since the foul happened before the score, it would have released the player. In this case, the player is not sent to the penalty box and keeps playing.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "Two opposing players have a grip on a ball when a broom's down is called. Which is correct ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Both players stay in position but cannot fight for the ball during broom's down",
      "BadAnswers": "Both players must release the ball to the ground, then can restart attacking it on broom's up\r\nBoth players must release the ball to the ground while broom's down, but can grab it again before broom's up.\r\nBoth players stay in position during broom's down and can try to get a better gripping on the ball before broom's up.",
      "AnswerExplanation": "It's a good idea to have an assistant watch the situation during broom's down.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "8",
      "QuestionText": "Assuming the player went in a bit farther than the official indicated, which of the following is true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "While the player did not went in exactly where the official requested him to, the difference is not significant enough to warrant a penalty.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/clumsynegligiblegoldenretriever?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "9",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Repeat Procedure",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The KO procedure requires the player to remove their broom, touch the hoop then remount their broom. Note that affecting play after a wrong procedure would have been a yellow card.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/sereneagedfanworms?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "10",
      "QuestionText": "Which of the followings are true?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Repeat Procedure",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "While the player start to remove its broom, the brooms does not leave their legs completely. The procedure is not correct. This is important during games where beater will want to gain time after being beat near a hoop.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/smallscarceacornweevil?autoplay=1"
    }
  ],
  "Reset": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for an illegal reset ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player physically forced behind the midfield line does not use its team's reset, under the condition that he or she makes the Quaffle cross the line back as soon as reasonnably possible.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/unitedwickeddromedary?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nTurnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player menaced by an opposing beater may cross the midline without it being an illegal reset, but still use a reset for his team.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/coordinatedthirstychimneyswift?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nTurnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player menaced by an opposing beater may cross the midline without it being an illegal reset, but still use a reset for his team.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/unitedredarchaeocete?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player crossing two lines in a single run is considered having used only one reset.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/astonishinghappygoluckyafghanhound?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "8",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player passing across two lines is considered having used only one reset, as it is a single action.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/enchantingrecentafricanelephant?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "9",
      "QuestionText": "QuestionResetRandom",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover",
      "BadAnswers": "Reset used\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player throwing behind crossing a reset line, or further into his own half, without anyone to receive perpetrates an illegal reset.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/talkativemadeupindianhare?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "10",
      "QuestionText": "QuestionResetRandom",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover",
      "BadAnswers": "Reset used\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nNo penalty",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player throwing behind crossing a reset line, or further into his own half, without knowing if anyone is here to receive perpetrates an illegal reset. Carefull not to penalize a player that knows where their teammates are without having to look.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/decimalshadowyleafhopper?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "11",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A player has to be there when the ball arrives for the pass to be considered valid, regardless of the state of the player at the beginning of the pass.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/ordinaryglorioUsqntelopegroundsquirrel?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "12",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the quaffle carrier's team?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Turnover",
      "BadAnswers": "Reset used\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The pass during the run back creates two separate reset actions, which triggers the illegal reset.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/graciouscalculatingandeancat?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "13",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for the Quaffle Carrier?",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Reset used\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nTurnover",
      "AnswerExplanation": "An opposing player jerking the Quaffle behind a reset line does not trigger the reset used, as long as the driving team makes it go back as soon as possible.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/wildhotargali?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "14",
      "QuestionText": "ResetDeadQuaffle",
      "GoodAnswers": "Reset used",
      "BadAnswers": "No penalty\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nTurnover",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A loose quaffle does not require a receiver to be reset.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/waterycontentgelada?autoplay=1"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "15",
      "QuestionText": "ResetAfterGetBack",
      "GoodAnswers": "No penalty",
      "BadAnswers": "Reset used\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellowCard\r\nRed Card\r\nTurnover",
      "AnswerExplanation": "The player who initiates a drive may carry or propel the quaffle backward\r\nacross one or both restrictor lines immediately upon the beginning of the\r\ndrive without it counting as a reset.",
      "NGB": "ALL",
      "Link": "https://gfycat.com/ifr/search/legalyellowishamazondolphin?autoplay=1"
    }
  ],
  "Scoring": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for goaltending ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The score is counter as good for the fouled team\r\nRed Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for illegaly resetting an opponent's hoop ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for unintentionally dislodging hoops repeatedly ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "4",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for recklessly dislodging a hoop ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "5",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for intentionnaly dislodging a hoop ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "6",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for moving a hoop intentionnaly ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "7",
      "QuestionText": "QuestionBlockingScoringQuaffleText",
      "GoodAnswers": "Red card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "SnitchPlay": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a seeker false start ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Blue Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Yellow Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "2",
      "QuestionText": "What of the following are true for a team that wants to decline a snitch catch ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "The catch can be just after a goal and before the referee confirmed the goal as good\r\nThe catch occured after a goal event (good or otherwise), and before the referee adjust his call for this event\r\nThe change in score must change whether the catch would end the period in a tie",
      "BadAnswers": "A team may decline any snitch catch",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    },
    {
      "Public Id": "3",
      "QuestionText": "QuestionUseBallInteractSnitchText",
      "GoodAnswers": "Yellow Card",
      "BadAnswers": "Turnover\r\nBlue Card\r\nRed Card\r\nBack to hoops",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ],
  "Substitution": [
    {
      "Public Id": "1",
      "QuestionText": "What is the penalty for a substitution violation ?",
      "GoodAnswers": "Repeat procedure",
      "BadAnswers": "Blue Card\r\nYellow Card\r\nRed Card",
      "AnswerExplanation": "A substitution violation is defined as an illegal substitution that did not affect play yet.",
      "NGB": "ALL"
    }
  ]
}